剧情回顾...
Previously on Lost...
我认为Michael已经向他们妥协了
I think Michael has been compromised.
Michael带我们去的营地 在那他们会设下陷阱
This camp Michael is leading you to--that is where they will set their trap.
- 我可以在不被发现的情况下上岸 - 怎么弄?
- And I can go ashore undetected. - How?
我们乘船去侦查一下
We will sail the boat and scout them.
这次他们会意识到我们来了
This time they will know that we are coming.
你好  Jack
Hi, Jack.
我是Juliet
I'm Juliet.
我的朋友在哪?
Where are my friends?
告诉我我的朋友在哪?
Tell me where my friends are!
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译： Singa 后期：梁良 双语字幕：chamber
是你干的吗?
Sun
这个芭蕾舞女是你打碎的吗?
那是谁干的?
是女仆干的
如果你说是女仆干的...
我会炒了她鱿鱼
你懂吗?
Sun
是谁打碎的?
是女仆干的
很好
Sun...开门
我很好
只是有点晕吐
Jin...等等
我丈夫说该回去了
My husband says it's time to leave.
他认为Jack他们不会来了
He doesn't think Jack and the others are coming.
烟已经点燃一天多了
It's been over a day since we lit the fire.
他们应该早来了
They should be here by now.
Jack知道我们在这里
Jack knows we're out here.
他就指望我们了
He's counting on our signal.
也许他们看不到黑烟
Perhaps he's not able to see the smoke.
如果他在我们北面  山会把他们视线挡住
If he's north of us, the mountains would block his view.
我们得继续开船沿着岸走 找个不会被山挡住的地方另点黑烟
We need to sail forward along the coast,Clear
the mountains and start another signal fire.
不
No
我答应Jack我们会点起黑烟的
I told Jack I would light a fire.
我不会食言
I'm not abandoning him.
Sayid说...
我们哪也不去
Sayid不是你的丈夫
我丈夫说我们得听他的 因为他是唯一一个知道怎么开船的
My husband thinks we have to do as
he says,Because he's the only one who knows how to sail.
但是他错了
But he's wrong.
我可以帮你开船
I can help you sail the boat.
感觉好点了么?
Are you feeling any better?
这汤是我自己弄的 如果你不喜欢的话也没办法
I made the soup myself,but I won't take it the wrong way if you don't like it.
你从没给我做过汤喝
You never made soup for me.
打扰你们了吗?
Am I interrupting something?
打不打扰有关系吗?
Would it really matter if you were?
有情况了
We have a situation.
Brian报告说
Brian radioed in.
那个伊拉克人发现了诱敌的村落了
The Iraqi found the decoy village.
很好
Good.
这正是我们想要的
It's what we wanted.
Brian跟着他去了岸边
Brian followed him back to the shore.
Ben  他们有艘帆船
Ben, they have a sailboat.
- 怎么弄到的?  - 我不知道
- How? - I have no idea.
就是说他们有艘船了
So they have a boat.
开着船绕圈可够他们忙的了
Sailing in circles will keep them busy.
他们会发现我们
They could find us.
- Ben... - 我在考虑
- Ben... - I'm thinking.
组一支队伍要多久?
How quickly can you put together a team?
一小时以内
Within the hour.
那就别浪费时间了
Then don't waste time talking to us.
嘿  Colleen
Hey, Colleen.
我要得到那条船
I want that boat.
迷失
第三季 第二集
很好听的警报声
Nice alarm clock.
吵醒我就不好了
I've woken up to worse.
你要一半鱼型饼干吗?
You want half a fish biscuit?
午饭  我们希望你保持体力
Lunch. We're gonna need you to keep up your strength.
可不是么?
Is that right?
Danny  等等
Danny, wait.
站着
Hold up.
你在看什么?
What are you looking at?
我得调整方向
我很抱歉  Jin
我不应该和你作对
特别是在Sayid面前
你确实不应该和我作对  在这期间
Sun
你为什么要跟来?
你知道我为什么要来的
我不想失去你
怎么了?
What's wrong?
因为我有丈夫了
What's wrong is I'm married.
是的
Right.
来吧
That.
Jae  我不能这样
我不能
我很抱歉...
Sun
等等...
Jae
真漂亮
但我不能戴着它...
Jin会问我是哪里来的
我不想再和别人分享你了
I don't want to share you anymore.
你的英语现在很好了
Your english is excellent now.
我们可以去美国了
We can go to america.
- 有人知道你在... - 没有
- Does anyone know you're... - No.
你在干什么?
滚出去...
先生
我很抱歉  我不知道...
穿上衣服
好了  就是这了
All right, here's the jig.
看到这些石头了吗?
See these rocks here?
这就是找你们来的原因
That's where you two come in.
你把它们挖松一点 你就负责把它们拉走
You're gonna chop 'em loose,and you're gonna haul 'em outta here.
你就让我这么穿着干活?
You expect me to work in this dress?
随你便了
It's up to you.
你愿意的话可以脱下来
You can take it off if you want.
你敢?
How dare you?
如果你们需要什么  举手
Now if you need anything, you raise your hand.
- 你们有10分钟吃午饭... - 我有个问题  老板
- You get ten minutes for lunch-- - I got a question, boss.
不许问问题
No questions.
就算她问了又怎么样?
She got to ask a question.
如果你们想逃  你们会被电击(Shocked)
If you try to run off, you will be shocked.
开枪(Shot)打我们?
Shot?
- 我们没有被警告的机会吗? - 电击  我是说电击
-Don't we even get a warning? -Shocked. I said shocked.
你们互相讲话  就会被电击
If you talk to each other, you'll be shocked.
你们互相碰触  就会被电击
You touch each other, you'll be shocked.
你们不努力干活  就会被电击
If you're slacking, you're gonna get shocked.
一句话  如果你做我不喜欢的事 你就会被电击
Matter of fact, you do anything at
all that pisses me off, you're gonna get shocked.
听懂了吗?
Okay?
在看到Jack之前我什么也不做
I'm not doing anything until I see Jack.
那只是四分之一的电量
Now that was a quarter charge.
还有问题吗?
You got any more questions?
一旦你有力气了 手推车就在那里
Soon as you're able to walk, wheelbarrow's right over there.
你想见我  先生?
进来
请坐
我们有麻烦了
这个人偷了我的东西
我要你去了结了他
他偷了什么?
这不重要
当然了
我会和他说的
说说有什么用
我要你去了结了他
我不能那么做
你当然可以
先生  这不是我的工作...
你的工作就是照我说的做
那我就不能再为你工作了
我辞职
你不会辞职的
这个人使我蒙羞
你娶了我的女儿  Jin
那你就是我儿子了
我的羞耻就是你的羞耻
我需要你去夺回我们家的尊严
那怎么会有一个码头?
Why should there be a dock all the way out here?
其他人
Others.
码头已经腐朽了
The dock's decaying.
杂草丛生
It's overgrown.
看起来很久没人用了
It looks like it hasn't been used in quite some time.
不管是谁建的  肯定都不在了
Whoever built it, they're not here now.
把船开过去
Let's bring the boat in.
绑在码头上  我们在海滩上生烟
We'll tie to the dock and build a fire on the beach.
这里可见性很好  Jack很远就可以看到
The visibility's excellent,And Jack will be able to see us from miles around.
安全么?
Safe?
是的  Jin
Yes, Jin.
这里当然安全
Of course it's safe.
回去干活
Get back to work.
听你的  老板
Whatever you say, boss.
小心点
Careful.
别让他们看到我在和你说话
Don't let them see you talking to me.
他们把你们关在笼子里吗?
Are they keeping you in the cages?
你还看到有别人吗?
Did you see another guy in there with you?
和我差不多大  叫Karl的
About my age, named Karl?
没有
No.
那里只有我和Sawyer
It's just Sawyer and me.
你们不应该被关在那里的
You're not even supposed to be in that cage.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
你是谁?
Who are you?
那件衣服哪来的?
Where'd you get that dress?
他们给我的
They gave it to me.
这是我的衣服
It's mine.
就给你吧
You can keep it.
你穿上比较好看
It looks better on you anyway.
等等
Wait. Wait.
很开心吗  小妞?
Having fun yet, freckles?
别老盯着我的屁股
Quit staring at my ass.
那就给别的让我看啊
Give me something else to stare at.
闭嘴
Shut up!
好的  老板
Yes, sir, boss.
谢谢
Thank you.
我还能做什么?
What else can I do?
去帮你的丈夫
Help your husband.
我们还需要很多木头
We need as much wood as we can find.
我们生的烟可够大的了
We're building quite a large fire.
我们得确信Jack会看到黑烟
We have to make sure Jack will see the smoke.
你为什么骗我  Sayid?
Why are you lying to me, Sayid?
你知道我骗了你什么  Sun?
And what would you know about lying, Sun?
你让我们冒生命危险
You're putting our lives in danger.
我很确信我们的朋友被抓了
I'm fairly certain our friends have been captured.
码头上都是足印
There are tracks all over the dock.
痕迹还很新  差不多是昨天的
They're fresh, as recent as yesterday.
你说过这个码头被闲置了
You said this dock was abandoned.
那也是一个谎言
That would be part of the lying you mentioned.
你不是为了我们的人而生烟
You're not building this fire for our people.
你是为了他们
You're building it for the others.
我想当他们看到烟后  会派一支调查队来
I suspect that when they see the
smoke, they'll send a scout party to investigate.
到那时已经是晚上了
By then it will be night.
当他们靠近  我们就伏击他们
When they arrive, I'll ambush them.
我会抓两个当人质  其余的都杀了
I'll take two of them hostage, and I'll kill the rest.
两个?
Two?
一个用来使他们和我们合作
One to make the other cooperate.
你要我怎么做?
What do you need me to do?
我很抱歉  但我需要你再瞒Jin二十分钟
I'm sorry, but I'm going to have to ask you
to lie to Jin for another 20 minutes.
为什么?
Why?
因为一旦火点起来了  要回去就太迟了
Because once the fire is lit, it will be too late to go back.
你回来了
今天过得怎样?
还不错
我去见你父亲了
是么?
他第一次叫我"儿子"
他为什么这么做?
他要我去传个消息
你会去做吗?
我不得不去
不  Jin
你不会去的
你认为有这么简单吗?
我们...
可以开始新生活
我们离开...
新生活?
如果我们离开  你的父亲会...
他不会知道我们在哪里的
你就不用老做这些事了
你不用...
我都是为了你  Sun
我这么做是因为你父亲希望我这么做
我这么做是因为...
这样做才能娶到你
那我到底做了什么才会嫁给你
Jin
你去哪?
去传达消息
枪
Gun.
我听不懂
I don't think I understand.
他说什么?
What is it?
他知道我们在做什么了
He knows what we're doing.
他知道这是一个陷阱
He knows it's a trap.
他说他懂得的英语比我想象的要多
He says he understands english etter than I think he does.
他知道我背叛了他
He knows I betrayed him.
枪
Gun.
你会用吗?
Can you handle one of these?
这是自动...
It's an automatic--
我想你在船上更安全
I think you'll be safer on the boat.
Sun...
如果一旦他们突破了我们 船里还有把枪
If by chance they get past us, there's another gun.
在橱柜下方的蓝油布下
It's inside the blue tarp beneath the galley counter.
如果他们突破了你们 就意味着我丈夫已经死了...
If they get past you, that means my husband is dead...
我就什么都不在乎了
and I won't care anymore.
听我说  枪就在油布下面
As I said, lhe gun is inside the tarp.
退后
Back off!
James
James.
把枪放下...
Put the gun down...
就现在
right now.
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
等等
你知道我是谁吗?
你知道我为什么来吗?
我很抱歉
现在你知道...
我要干什么了吧
我很抱歉
抱歉
滚出国去
听懂了吗?
你滚出去...
不要再回来
开始新生活
一旦我知道你回来了...
或和国内有什么联系的话...
你就完了
懂了吗?
这里没有你这号人了
我想他们不会来了
I don't think they're coming.
我要你放我下船
I want you to let me off this boat.
我办不到
I can't do that.
为什么?
Why not?
我没这个权利
That's not my decision to make.
- 你应该知道我们有五个人... - 小声点
-You realize there are five of my friends up there-- -Lower your voice.
好吧
站住
不  你不会的  Sun
No, you won't, Sun.
我知道你  Sun-Hwa Kwon
I know you, Sun-Hwa Kwon.
你不会杀人的
And I know you're not a killer.
不管你们怎么想  我们都不是敌人
Despite what you may think,I am not the enemy.
我们都不是敌人
We are not the enemy.
但如果你开枪了...
But if you shoot me...
那我们就注定是敌人了
that's exactly what we'll become.
站住
我会开枪的
I will. I'll shoot you.
Sun
Sun!
不
你不应该来的
爸爸
你来干什么?
我和这个年轻人的父亲有生意往来
我说过他是从阳台上跳下来的
他一定是不齿自己的作为了
现在...
回到你丈夫那去
爸爸
你会告诉Jin吗?
要告诉也不应该由我来说
我不知道失去你我会怎样
失去你们
我很抱歉我把你们扯进来
I'm sorry I dragged you into this.
请对你的丈夫说 下一次  我会听他的
And please communicate to your husband, the next time, I will listen to him.
我们得走了
We should go.
还要走很多的路
We have a long walk ahead of us.
你没事吧?
You okay?
好得不能再好了
Never better.
你到底在想什么?
What the hell were you thinking?
我情不自禁
I couldn't help myself.
你挥动镐的动作太美了
You just looked so damn cute swinging that pickax.
你很适合做苦工啊  小妞
Chain gang looks good on you, freckles.
Sawyer
Sawyer.
他们中有两个打架很厉害
Two of those guards got some real fight in 'em.
其他人就不怎么担心了
Rest of 'em, I ain't that much worried about.
被那个魁梧的家伙打一拳还真够你受的
That heavyset guy packs a hell of a punch.
头发很乱的小子受过军事训练 但是不得以的情况下我还是能撂倒他的
Shaggy-Haired kid's got some sort of martial arts
training, but I think I could take him if I had to.
还有...那些电击的东西上有保险装置
Oh, and F.Y.I., those zapper things got a safety on 'em.
当你拿着来福枪的时侯   看到他们的表情了吗?
Did you see the look on their faces when you got a hold of that rifle?
我猜他们很多人从没见过枪战
I'm guessin' most of these boys never seen any real action.
但是那个拿枪指着你的金发女人...
But that blonde who had a gun to your head...
她会开枪的  毫无疑问
she woulda shot you, no problem.
她为什么叫你James?
Why'd she call you James?
因为那是我的名字
'Cause that's my name.
我还注意到了
I noticed somethin' else, too.
你的味道就像草莓
You taste like strawberries.
你的味道就像鱼形饼干
You taste like fish biscuits.
那我们该怎么办?
So what do we do now?
那么...
Well, shortcake...
我们只有等这些混蛋自己犯错了
now we wait for these bastards to make a mistake.
迟早  他们会放松警惕
Sooner or later, they're gonna let their guard down.
一旦他们这么做了 我们就让他们该呆在哪里就呆在哪里
And when they do, we're gonna be thereto put 'em in their place.
你好  Jack
Hello, Jack.
你知道么  Jack?
You know what's crazy Jack?
一周前  你和我的情况正好相反
A week ago, you and I were in exactly the opposite situation.
我是那个被锁起来的人 而你是那个走进来的人
I was the one locked up, and you were the one coming in for visits.
并且我知道你很生气 因为我骗了你关于我是谁的事
And I know that you were angry, that I lied to you about who I was
但是...你怪我吗?
but...Hell ! Do you blame me?
我是说  我们面对事实吧
I mean, let's face it.
如果我跟你说我就是你和你朋友 指的"其他人"中的一员
If I'd have told you I was one of those people, that you and your
friends have been calling "others" all this time,
那就会招来Sayid和他的拳头
it would've been right back to Sayid and his...fists.
不是吗?
Wouldn't it?
你想要什么?
What do you want from me?
我想改变你的...
I want for you to change your...
想法
perspective.
那么第一步就是诚恳地向你介绍我是谁
And the first step in doing that would be
for me to...be decent enough to introduce myself honestly, so...
你好
Hi.
我叫Benjamin Linus  我一生都生活在这个岛上
My name is Benjamin Linus, and I've lived on this island all my life.
你不和我握手吗?
You're not gonna shake?
带进来
Bring it in, please.
Kate和Sawyer在哪?
Where are Kate and Sawyer?
他们很好  就在附近
They're fine, and they're close.
现在我只能告诉你这些
That's all I'm able to tell you right now.
你可以告诉我任何你想说的
You can tell me anything you want.
很好
Fair enough.
我就是想告诉你这些
It's all I want to tell you.
我会说的很简单的  Jack
I'm gonna make this really simple, Jack.
如果你合作的话  我们就送你回家
If you cooperate, we send you home.
合作什么?
Cooperate with what?
- 到时候会告诉你的... - 现在就告诉我
- When the time is right, I'll tell you. - You tell me now.
耐心点  Jack
Patience, Jack.
- 耐心点 - 家
- Patience. - Home.
就是你送Walt和Micheal去的地方吗?
Is that where you sent Walt and Michael?
是的
Yes.
如果你可以离开这个岛  你怎么还会在这?
If you could leave this island, why would you still be here?
是的  Jack
Yes, Jack.
我们为什么要在这?
Why would we be here?
你在说谎
You're lying.
你和我们一样也被困在这里了
You're stuck here just like we are.
- 你不知... - 你们的飞机在2004年9月22日坠毁
-You dont have any... -Your flight crashed on september 22, 2004.
今天是11月29号
Today is november 29th.
就是说你们在岛上已经69天了
That means you've been on our island for 69 days.
是的  我们和外界有联系  Jack
And, yes, we do have contact with the outside world, Jack.
所以我们知道在这69天里 George W. Bush连任了总统
That's how we know that during those 69 days,
your fellow americans reelected George W. Bush,
Christopher Reeve死了 并且波士顿红袜队拿了联赛冠军
Christopher Reeve has passed away, Boston Red Sox won the world series.
什么?
What?
你想让我相信的话就不应该说是红袜队夺冠
If you wanted me to believe this,you probably
should've picked somebody else besides the Red Sox.
不  他们在决赛中连下3场赢了美国人队
No, they were down three games to none
against the Yankees in the league championship,
这已经是他们的8连胜了
and then they won eight straight.
是啊是啊
Sure, sure.
当然是这样了
Of course they did.
红袜队的球迷渴望了很久了
Red Sox fans have longed to hear it.
波士顿红袜队是世界冠军
The Boston Red Sox are world champions!
在完成对对手的横扫之后
A clean sweep of the St Louis Cardinals,
红袜队在Busch体育场中央庆祝
and the Red Sox celebrate in the middle of the diamond here at Busch stadium.
那就是家  Jack  就在玻璃的那边
That's home, Jack, right there on the other side of that glass.
如果你听我的  如果你相信我
And if you listen to me, if you trust me,
如果到时你按我说的做 我就带你去那里
if you do what I tell you when the time comes, I'll take you there.
我会带你回家
I will take you home.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■